Hello friends, how are you all, I hope
you all are doing well. In today's
episode, the registration for
ICICI Bank CSP has started for all of you in the current CSC
and all of you will definitely get the
SP of ICICI Bank
and the best thing is that friends, now in the
CSP that
ICICI Bank is providing, you do
not have to get any update from any bank manager, the
district manager will
not be able to do any formula for you, you can apply for it yourself, you
will open your account yourself and
you can just apply
and get it yourself and you will
not need to go around any district manager,
friends, this is a big good news,
so in today's video we will know how you have to
click and
what documents will be requested for such bank CSP, that
you should check, the
documents will be required, we will know everything in this video,
so friends, before starting the video, I would
like to make a small
request to you, if you are new to my channel, then please
subscribe to the channel and like the video
because Seva Kendra CSC and DAX
Latent, you are half  Like the minute video
to complete this video
on your computer and here I have kept it open in
which
I have kept the information for it open,
here I have subscribed here,
what you have to do is here in CR,
after first appointing you,
subscribe here and it should open here, you have to
click on appointment here,
as if you will click on them, here the day before yesterday
your first step is written register
and in the second it is written New Year, if
you have any lady at this point then you
will click on edit, inside wise you used to
click on New Year, so now I am
telling you the new way, so you have to click on news,
after clicking on news you have to click on time, as soon as
you click on submit, the
list of all the documents will open in front of you,
what documents are going to be required in your form,
all this information has been given,
friends, first of all it has been told here
that you should have this photo, here your
address proof and ID proof should be there,
outside and inside photo of your Bank Mitra center
Inside and outside, so now
keep it ready, you should have a savings account
and subscribe for quality, it should be
here
that its darkness is fine, after this you have to
click on continue, click on continue
and friends, as you
click, it will open here,
friends, I have already
registered here, hence it
cannot appear in front of me, you can simply comment and subscribe,
then if you face any problem, then
you can subscribe by commenting, now we will
cut it to subscribe and there will be
no need to subscribe from home, after
coming here you
subscribe,
after giving your direct link here you have to click on,
like click on, now
his mobile number 66 will be linked, an OTP will
go on it and you have to enter the OTP here,
after that you have to click on verify ok,
then this 10th page will open in front of you,
after this you have to click
on the registration option, after coming here
you have to click on agent registration,
pimpl money  If you click on this, here the
option of agent's KYC will appear in front of you,
you have to click on this, if you do it
basically then you will be
asked for your Aadhaar number here,
you have to give your Aadhaar number,
after this you will be asked for your finger,
which you want to put,
click on it, left or right, whatever you want to do,
friends, I made a mistake here,
I have set the mask here,
I will change my device now,
after this the further process will be possible, so
I cut it and
open Facebook, then here
you have to select the device,
innocent or whatever your device is, you have to
select it here and after this
you have come in the worry fear life,
click on this entry system again
and we have to click on return of entry,
okay, now you have to give your Aadhaar number, let's go
and after clicking on relation,
you have to click on cancer,
okay, our biometric device is
ready, I have cut it,
now we  We have to click on this,
friends, there might be some problem in the portal right now
or the server might be busy
because at this time the traffic is very high
on the ISI portal, so I am not able to proceed further,
you just put your finger like this,
enter your Aadhar number here and complete your
KYC process,
after completing it,
you have to open the printer
and after printing, I will tell you the further
process, what you have to do,
after knowing this you have to complete it, in the
second step
you have to click on treatment download, now it is opening, let's wait
and note that the
reference of Aadhar is not getting subscribed
due to flying, I will tell you, you
people have to click on the document download
option here like a proof, then here
you have to print this cover of subscription by opening it
and here you have to
click on your bank details and then
in the field there, then you subscribe to the channel
and after 15 days I will
subscribe you here  After visiting here
we submit it
and there your account gets doubled,
but that shrink is
given to you there and you fall into ICICI Bank
ABC, so in this way you
can easily do ICICI Bank, friends
if you face any problem in this process
then you must tell us by commenting,
because of being cursed I am not able to complete it for you, so
friends subscribe to our video.